adchakra.net 2017-12-18

# PRIVACY POLICY - Adchakra

**www.adchakra.com** is completely committed to protect its users’ privacy. We request you to read this privacy policy before you fill the “Contact us” form at adchakra.com and agree to our Privacy Policy defined below. This will help you understand how your personal and business information will be managed at adchakra.com, as you use our service for your business benefits.

**Information we collect**  
The “Online Enquiry Form” and “Contact Us” page will ask for your name, phone number, email address and nature of enquiry about your business so that we can assist you better with your query.

Apart from the above enquiry form, we collect comprehensive information regarding our website and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth.

**Use of Information**  
The information collected is used to improve our marketing and promotional efforts to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our website’s content, layout and service exclusively to get hold of maximum business opportunities. We may perhaps make use of your gathered information to service your Account with us, together with, however not restricted to inspecting troubles, resolve disagreements and imposing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade any personally identifying information of our users.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure of Information**  
Adchakra.com does not disclose or share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Adchakra unless it is for Legal reasons necessitating to:

  1. meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  2. enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
  3. detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  4. protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Adchakra, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**Security Measures**  
We take up commercially logical protection ways to put off unlawful access, preserve data precision and guarantee proper use of information.

You should also recognize that no data communication over the Internet or any wireless network can be assured to be absolutely protected. Though we attempt our level best to protect your information, even after knowing that no website or company, together with ourselves, can extremely guarantee or promise the safety of any information you send out to us and, you do so at your own risk. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The amended Privacy Policy will be posted here for your purpose. The amended policy will be effective from the day it is posted on the website.

**Your feedback**  
Adchakra.com welcomes your constant input on the topic of Privacy Policy or services presented to you. You could mail us your remarks and reactions at [contact@perceptknorigin.com](mailto:contact@perceptknorigin.com)
